Hitesh Jadhav

hiteshjadhav868@gmail.com | +91-9765946426 | GitHub | LinkedIn

ABOUT ME

2+ Years of experience in developing web applications using ReactJS. I am a self-motivated, multi-faceted, Quality-focused, creative, dedicated, and Results-driven professional seeking a position as a frontend developer with JavaScript Juice where I can use my skills as a web developer to enhance the user experience.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Associate Software Developer, Motivity labs Inc, Hyderabad

September 2022 - May 2023

- Worked on application which is similar to job portal.
- Integrated pagination feature into a job portal application using JavaScript, material UI.
- Developed number of modules with React.js library.
- Worked CSS framework like Bootstrap 4.
- Implemented chart using chart.js.
- Used the React component library like material UI to implement Data Grid.
- Adept at learning new technologies and tools quickly.
- Experience in creating and consuming RESTful APIs.
- Implemented user authentication and authorization features using JSON Web Tokens.

Jr. Web Developer, Abhiyantrix Tech LLP, Mumbai

January 2021 – July 2022

- Implement UI components.
- Used JavaScript concepts to build the components.
- Worked on Responsive designs. Used flexbox, media query.

Software programmer/associate analyst, Ugam Solutions, thane

July 2019 –October 2020

- Worked on multiple projects.
- Used web technology like HTML, CSS and JavaScript for enhancing the UI and User Experience and making pages more interactive.
- Collaborated with designers and back-end developers to build responsive and interactive UI components.
- Worked on decipher platform, qualtrics.
- Worked on different clients from various industries like healthcare, media, entertainment, and automobile. (Clients NRG, Screen Engine, escalent-MSi)

SKILLS

- **Programming Languages** JavaScript, HTML5, CSS3.
- Web Development React.js, Bootstrap, Material-UI, RESTful APIs
- **Databases** MongoDB, Mongoose.
- **Backend** Node.js, Express

EDUCATION

RGIT, Mumbai University, B.E, computer Engineering

2015 - 2019

Diploma (computer engineering), GVAP polytechnic, karjat.

2012 - 2015

Fullstack development course - Fynd (Shopsense Retail Tech. ltd) training

Mar 2024 - Jun 2024